Justin M Carbone

14016 Bora Bora Way, Marina Del Rey, CA 90292 Justin.M.Carbone@gmail.com | (516) 971-3627

linkedin.com/in/jcarbone13

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A motivated, creative professional who produces for the best results with the brands, clients, and platforms. Core focus on digital & social media sales with a strong emphasis on SaaS, video, influencer, creative, technology, and branded partnerships. In addition: print, broadcast, and experiential media sales experience. Skill set includes business development, marketing, content creation, media planning, ad operations, leading presentations, and knowledge of the current trends in the marketplace.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Hyfn Director, Client Partnerships

Los Angeles, CA June 2018 - Present

- Responsible for driving new revenue for various advertising and agency partners across our suite of services through the key five social platforms, closed \$8.6M worth of new revenue.
- Build on existing advertising and agency partnership relationships, pushing incremental revenue across the various platforms through our SaaS and/or managed service, content creation and technology development services;
 Driven \$1.2M worth of incremental revenue for existing partnerships
- Work closely with our social platform partners such as Facebook, Snap Inc to push upcoming product, and service launches to advertising and agency partners based on their national and local business needs
- Partner and manage internal relationships with media and marketing teams to deliver a strategic solution-based plan for our advertising and agency partners
- Work with legal on various agreements including but not limited to mutual service agreements with clients.

DUNNHUMBY: BzzAgent

Director of Business Development

August 2017 - June 2018

- Founding sales executive for Western US region handling business and revenue development for the CPG vertical
- Responsible for building list of CPG brands looking to expand their influencer marketing strategy on various social platforms through client retention and new business; increased client bandwidth by 40%
- Led and managed full sales cycle, overseeing account management on pricing, planning, and packaging for potential CPG clients

ZEFR

Channel Sales/Cross Platform Account Manager

July 2016 - August 2017

- Conceptualized and executed new product strategy and implementation for enterprise partnerships across domestic and international markets to allow for strategic revenue growth and internal stakeholder alignment
- Researched, analyzed, and operationalized potential sources for business development and new revenue streams including, but not limited to, Channel Sales, Cross-Platform, revised suite of products, and new ideations
- Lead on the operations and performance task force for enterprise-level projects including pricing, planning, and packaging for potential strategic partners

SWEETY HIGH

Branded Sales/Partnerships Account Executive (Consultant)

December 2015 - May 2016

- One of two founding members of internal sales organization focused on developing all aspects of the sales processes, infrastructure, and liaison with outside sales consultants to create necessary foundation for business development and revenue creation
- Packaged and pitched branded content deals to advertisers targeting the Gen Z female demographic (ages 10-16) with a digital revenue goal of \$1.5M which garnered initial market awareness and introductory conversations
- Executed various sales and marketing collateral, as well as lead conversations on pricing and packing for potential partners

VIACOM NETWORKS, INC: BET Networks

New York, NY

Digital Account Executive

August 2014 - November 2015

- Responsible for driving \$2.6M digital revenue across a dedicated list of agencies and key clients, such as OMD, Mediavest, Horizon, Hill Holiday, Samsung, Coca-Cola, P&G, Brown-Forman, Walmart, Mars, GEICO, and Warner Brothers with target hit and exceeded (106%) of 2014 revenue goal
- Manage sales cycle of all accounts including upfront and scatter negotiations of current and new clientele

- Maintained and built consistent relationships with current and prospective advertising partners and internal sales support teams ensuring a return on investment for both clients and division
- Cultivated presentations, verbal and written pre/post sell efforts, and account maintenance post sale, which created continued growth in revenue for division
- Worked closely with VP, Digital Strategy, Operations, & BD and Digital Sales Director to create the BET Networks Omnichannel strategy to solidify long-term, multiplatform partnerships to create and drive new business opportunities outside of standard sales channels

Flavorpill Media

Digital Account Executive

January 2014 - August 2014

- Responsible for driving digital revenue across a dedicated list of client and agency contacts looking for engaging content and programs through digital and experiential media which allowed key clients to partner on original video and event content
- Developed and lead prospective clients through presentations and pitches which allowed for strong brand recognition and presence in the digital/online market place which allowed for \$500k in revenue inclusive of strategic partnerships while still retaining full brand integrity
- Charged with managing all facets of the sales cycle, including: prospecting, brainstorming, presenting, negotiating
 and closing the sale, which lead to return and new clientele business across the various company product and
 services

Martha Stewart Living Digital Sales

Senior Digital Account Manager

April 2012 - December 2013

- Responsible for driving digital revenue across a dedicated list of accounts and agencies such as Zenith, Optimedia, Mediavest, and Essence
- Managed all aspects of sales accounts including estimating costs, managing budgets and allocating resources internally and externally
- Cultivated and grew relationships with clients, agency contacts, and various departments within the company by ensuring timely and professional attention

Digital Account Manager

- Partnered with Digital Director to increase revenue by providing updated progress on various high priority accounts, such as P&G, Coke, Microsoft, Mars, and Samsung
- Built strong agency and client relationships at all levels, created media plans and presentations, and accurately managed sales pipeline
- Oversaw execution and digital recaps on complex and/or customized digital media campaigns, and proactively worked to generate new business and drive renewals

VIACOM NETWORKS, INC: Digital Entertainment & Music Ad Sales Client Service Representative (CSR)

November 2010 - April 2012

- Responsible for full day-to-day support of three Account Executives and five Account Managers including, but not limited to, managing campaigns, the clearance of payment from the agency, following up on all correspondence in a timely manner, pricing, and inventory
- Assisted in creating media plans and decks to secure business by conveying our reach and audience demographic to best fit the client needs
- Managed agency relationships with Group M, Essence, and Mediavest through daily correspondence which effectively built relationships for continued current and future business

EDUCATION

HOFSTRA UNIVERSITY Bachelors, English Hempstead, NY

ADDITIONAL

- Technical Proficient in Microsoft Office Suite, SalesForce, MagAdvisor, Sol bright, Freewheel, Doubleclick Software, Neilson, ComScore, @plan, Moat, Xerox Suite, Seller Crowd, Clearslide, Basecamp, Twitter, Facebook, Pinterest, Snapchat, Instagram, Pipedrive, AdWords, DOMO for Business, Facebook for Business, Mindbody for business, Apollo, Boostr, Hubspot
- Volunteer SOFAR Sounds MC & Guest Liaison (June 2016 Present), Movember Ambassador (October 2017 Present), Ohana-Kane Project Community Volunteer (October 2018 Present)
- **Personal** Enjoys organizational development, team building, and motivating others. Making connections, learning about new ways to facilitate and onboard technological developments. Passionate about all things Film, Entertainment, and Fitness related.